A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Japanese Studies and Korean Studies, Record Group 3, Series 7 FA1775
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) program files, 1946-1995; 1; 14.15 Cubic Feet 36.75 document boxes: 34.75 letter size boxes and 2 legal size boxes
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1987 Meeting - Tentative agenda, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 377)
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars (CIES) - The Japan-United States Education Commission (Fulbright Program), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 378-379)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1987 Meeting (Box 36, Folder 380)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1988 Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 381)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) general file, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 382)
  - Modern Japanese philosophy, William LaFleur and Thomas Kasulis - Papers and reports, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 383-384)
  - Modern Japanese philosophy, William LaFleur and Thomas Kasulis, 1986-1989 (Box 36, Folder 385)
  - Modern Japanese philosophy, William LaFleur and Thomas Kasulis, 1969-1987 (Box 36, Folder 386)
  - Construction of the Body and Sexuality, Brett de Bary, J. Victor Koschmann, and Naoki Sakai, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 387)
  - History of Japanese Studies, John Hall, 1984-1987 (Box 37, Folder 388)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Rocky Mountain and Southwest, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 389)
  - International History of East Asia, Ronald Toby and William Atwell, 1983-1988 (Box 37, Folder 390)
  - International History of East Asia, Ronald Toby and William Atwell - Conference papers, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 391)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) grant application - Negotiating Public and Private Interests in Contemporary Japan, 1985-1989 (Box 37, Folder 392)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Triangle East Asia Colloquium (TEAC), 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 393)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Southern, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 394)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Midwest, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 395)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Rocky Mountain and Southwest, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 396)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - New England, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 397)
- Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) program files, 1945-1995; 2; 5.77 Cubic Feet 15 document boxes: 14.25 letter size boxes and .75 legal size box
  This subseries documents several aspects of the Social Science Research Council's Joint Committee on Korean Studies' (JCKS) operations including committee administration and meetings, grant funding for JCKS, collaboration and communication with other organizations focused on Korean Studies and cross-cultural Korea-United States cross-cultural research, JCKS's place within SSRC research programming, particularly programming for East Asia, planning and decisions for JCKS's grants and fellowship programs, and support for other conferences and research projects.
  Files pertaining to JCKS administration concern committee membership, SSRC staffing support, and committee meetings. Meeting files contain correspondence, agendas, notes, and minutes documenting meeting planning and preparation, proceedings, and follow-up activities.
  Files show that the JCKS sought and received grant funding from organizations like the Henry Luce Foundation, the Korea Foundation, and the Korea Research Foundation.
  Whereas grant and fellowship files in Subseries 7.5 and 7.6 concern individual applicants, files pertaining to the JCKS grants and fellowship programs in this subseries document planning, funding, and decisions for award years at large.
  Another area of focus for the JCKS outside of its grants and fellowship programs was the Regional Seminar Program. Files concerning these seminars document their administration and meetings. Additionally, there are files documenting the preparation and proceedings of the various research conferences, projects, and publications the JCKS supported. Because most of the research with which the JCKS engaged pertained to South Korea (Republic of Korea (ROK)), the JCKS had a significant interest in developing more knowledge around North Korea (Democratic People's Republic of Korea (DPRK)).
  - Wilson Center Report on Korean Studies, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 398)
  - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP) report - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS), 1986 (Box 37, Folder 399)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) history, undated (Box 38, Folder 400)
  - Korean Neo-Confucianism, Michael Kalton, 1985-1990 (Box 38, Folder 401)
  - Politics and Culture in Modern Korea, David McCann and Michael Robinson, undated (Box 38, Folder 402)
  - Report on Korean Studies in the United States, Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) and Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 403)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1988 Meeting - Tentative agenda (Box 38, Folder 404)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1993 Meeting - Preparation, 1988-1993 (Box 38, Folder 405)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1992 Meeting - Preparation, 1991-1993 (Box 38, Folder 406)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1992 Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 407)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) announcement of fellowships, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 408)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget, 1990 September 25 (Box 38, Folder 409)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) North Korea initiative, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 410)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) other projects, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 411)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1990 Meeting (Box 38, Folder 412)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1992 Meeting - Agenda (Box 38, Folder 413)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1992 Meeting - Follow-up (Box 38, Folder 414)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1992 Meeting - Grant proposal materials (Box 38, Folder 415)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1991 Meeting (Box 38, Folder 416)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1991 Meeting (Box 39, Folder 417)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Information for fellows and grantees, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 418)
  - SSRC brochure in Korean, undated (Box 39, Folder 419)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) delegation visit to Korea - Follow-up, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 420)
  - Ford Foundation Area Studies Grant report - Korea, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 421)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP) correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 39, Folder 422)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP) and committee membership, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 423)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Area Studies crisis, 1989-1990 (Box 39, Folder 424)
  - SSRC East Asia Program China trip - Committee on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China (CSCPRC), 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 425)
  - Korean War conference, David Halloway, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 426)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) fellow and grantee progress and terminal reports, 1984-1991 (Box 39, Folder 427)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) funding initiatives, 1986-1991 (Box 39, Folder 428)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) program staffing, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 429)
  - State and Society in Contemporary Korea, Hagen Koo, 1987-1993 (Box 39, Folder 430)
  - Political conflict in Korea, B.C. Koh and Chong Lim Kim, 1986-1990 (Box 39, Folder 431)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Problems and Policy Executive Committee, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 432)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Problems and Policy Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 433)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) member C.V.s, 1992-1995 (Box 39, Folder 434)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - James Larson correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 435)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Seed Money Grants for Comparative and Transnational Research Projects, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 436)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1992-1993 Meetings, 1990-1993 (Box 39, Folder 437)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1992 Meeting - Minutes (Box 40, Folder 438)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1988-1989 membership roster, circa 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 439)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 40, Folder 440-441)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) report to Henry Luce Foundation, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 442)
  - SSRC East Asia Program staff search, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 443)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) committee member acceptances, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 444)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) committee member reappointments, 1988-1991 (Box 40, Folder 445)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) committee membership, 1986-1989 (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) committee membership, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 447)
  - Korean Studies in America: Options for the Future, The Wilson Center East Asia Program, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 448)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) committee member appointments, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 449)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) potential committee members, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 450)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) departing committee members, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 451)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) fundraising, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 452)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) grant status summaries for grants to JCKS, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 453)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget sheets, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 454)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 455)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget summaries, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 456)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 457)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Henry Luce Foundation Field Development grant budget, 1990 April 16 (Box 41, Folder 458)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1990 Meetings - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 459)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) North Korea trip - Expenses, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 460)
  - Korean Studies in America: Options for the Future, The Wilson Center East Asia Program, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 461)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Henry Luce Foundation, 1989-1992 (Box 41, Folder 462)
  - Wilson Center Task Force on establishing Priorities for Korean Studies in America, 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 463)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) correspondence - Korean Studies field, 1986-1989 (Box 41, Folder 464)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget, 1988-1990 (Box 41, Folder 465)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Vietnam exchanges, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 466)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Communities in Question: Religion and Authority in East and Southeast Asia - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 467)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Communities in Question: Religion and Authority in East and Southeast Asia, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 468-469)
  - Korean religion volume, 1980-1985 (Box 41, Folder 470)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1991 Meeting - Follow-up, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 471)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) history and meeting minutes, 1988-1991 (Box 41, Folder 472)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) fellowship guide, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 473)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) announcements, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 474)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Miscellaneous administration, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 475)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship and Advanced Research Grant 1993-1994 application summaries (Box 42, Folder 476)
  - Delegation to China report - The Development of Sociology in China, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 477)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Henry Luce Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 478)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) discussion with Luce Foundation regarding North Korea Initiative, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 479)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Korea Foundation grant proposal, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 480)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) membership, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 481)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) grant proposal for Dissertation Fellowship Program, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 482)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Korea Foundation grant proposal, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 483)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) miscellaneous notes, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 484)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget - Ford Foundation grant status summaries, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 485)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) plans for SSRC President David Featherman visit to Seoul, South Korea, 1992 January (Box 42, Folder 486)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant awardees - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 487)
  - Korean Popular Religion, Griffin Dix and Laurel Kendall, 1978-1987 (Box 42, Folder 488)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Regional Seminar Program - Midwest, 1983-1985 (Box 42, Folder 489)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Regional Seminar Program - Northwestern, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 490)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Regional Seminar Program - Midwest, 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 491)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Grant and fellowship applications, conferences, and information on Korea, part 1, 1979-1991 (Box 42, Folder 492-493)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) - Grant and fellowship applications, conferences, and information on Korea, part 2, 1979-1991 (Box 43, Folder 494-495)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Columbia University Seminar on Korea, 1975-1983 (Box 43, Folder 496)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1977 Meeting (Box 43, Folder 497)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1976 Meeting (Box 43, Folder 498)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1976 Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 499)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1975-1976 grant awards (Box 43, Folder 500)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1975 Meeting (Box 43, Folder 501)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1975 Meeting (Box 43, Folder 502)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1974 Meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 503)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1974 Meeting (Box 43, Folder 504)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1975 grant awards (Box 43, Folder 505)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1973-1974 grant awards (Box 43, Folder 506)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1973 Meeting (Box 43, Folder 507)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1972 Meeting (Box 43, Folder 508)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) annual reports, 1981-1985 (Box 43, Folder 509)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) annual reports segments, 1968-1980 (Box 44, Folder 510)
  - SSRC Items articles and announcements, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 511)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget, 1974-1982 (Box 44, Folder 512)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) membership - Rosters and appointments, 1973-1980 (Box 44, Folder 513)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) membership - C.V.'s, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 514)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) membership - C.V.'s, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 515)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) membership - C.V.'s, 1984-1986 (Box 44, Folder 516)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) membership - C.V.'s, 1976-1980 (Box 44, Folder 517)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) general correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 44, Folder 518)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) general file, 1983-1986 (Box 44, Folder 519)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) general file, 1981-1986 (Box 44, Folder 520)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1982 Meeting (Box 44, Folder 521)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1982 Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 522)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1981 Meeting, 1980-1982 (Box 44, Folder 523)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1980-1981 grant awards, 1979-1981 (Box 45, Folder 524)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) grants - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 525)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1979 Meeting (Box 45, Folder 526)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1980 Meeting (Box 45, Folder 527)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1979 Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 528)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1978 Meeting, 1976-1978 (Box 45, Folder 529)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1977-1978 grant awards, 1976-1978 (Box 45, Folder 530)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) 1979-1980 grant awards (Box 45, Folder 531)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1978 Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 532)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1977 Meeting (Box 45, Folder 533)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1983 Meeting - Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 534)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1985 Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 45, Folder 535)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1986 Meeting (Box 45, Folder 536)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1984 Meeting - Agenda, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 537)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1984 Meeting (Box 45, Folder 538)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1983 Meeting - Agenda, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 539)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1983 Meeting, 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 540)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) meetings - Committee membership, 1981-1983 (Box 45, Folder 541)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant grantees questionnaire - Responses, 1985-1987 (Box 46, Folder 542-543)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 544)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 545)
  - SSRC - Korea without Raquel Ovryn Rivera's revisions, circa 1989 (Box 46, Folder 545)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - SSRC - Korea with Raquel Ovryn Rivera's revisions, circa 1989 (Box 46, Folder 545)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States - Kong Dan Oh and Ralph Hassig resumes, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 546)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 547)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 548)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 549)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) Survey files 1988-1989, circa 1989 (Box 46, Folder 549)
  - Question and Answer files for Korea Research Foundation (KRF) Survey, circa 1989 (Box 46, Folder 549)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 550)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States - Distribution, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 551)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 552)
  - Korea Research Foundation (KRF) funded survey on Korean Studies in the United States, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 553)
  - Korean film, Perry Bialor, 1984-1985 (Box 46, Folder 554)
  - Personal testimony workshop, Laurel Kendall, 1988-1990 (Box 46, Folder 555)
  - Personal testimony, Laurel Kendall, 1986-1988 (Box 46, Folder 556)
  - Popular religions in East and Southeast Asia, 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 557)
  - Popular religions in East and Southeast Asia, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 558)
  - Popular religions in East and Southeast Asia, 1973-1987 (Box 47, Folder 559)
  - Korean Studies Journal, James Palais, 1983-1986 (Box 47, Folder 560)
  - Korean Studies Journal, James Palais, 1977-1982 (Box 47, Folder 561)
  - Political Economy of East Asia, Hagen Koo, 1983-1986 (Box 47, Folder 562-563)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) general correspondence, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 564)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) miscellaneous proposals, 1945-1982 (Box 47, Folder 565)
  - Japan and Korea social change and economic development, Chae-Jin Lee and Cameron Hurst, 1980-1983 (Box 48, Folder 566-567)
  - Japan and Korea social change and economic development, Chae-Jin Lee and Cameron Hurst, 1978-1985 (Box 48, Folder 568)
  - New religions in East and Southeast Asia, 1986-1988 (Box 48, Folder 569-570)
  - Korean Buddhism, Peter Lee, 1981-1985 (Box 48, Folder 571)
  - Korean political science, Han-Kyo Kim, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 572)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Korea Colonial Period Working Group, 1978-1983 (Box 49, Folder 573)
  - SSRC Newly Industrialized Countries (NICs) Working Group, 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 574-575)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) North Korea scholarly exchange - Advisory Committee on Scholarly Exchange with North Korea, 1974-1983 (Box 49, Folder 576-577)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) North Korea scholarly exchange - Gari Keith Ledyard aborted trip, 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 578)
  - Leadership effectiveness in Thailand and Korea, Martin Chemers and Roya Ayman - SSRC Southeast Asia research grant application, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 579)
  - Research Center for Peace and Unification of Korea - Korea and World Affairs: A Quarterly Review, Vol. 11, No.3, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 580)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1987 Meeting - Agenda, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 581)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1987 Meeting - Agenda, 1985-1987 (Box 50, Folder 582)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1986 Meeting - Agenda (Box 50, Folder 583)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) general file, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 584)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1989 Meeting - Agenda, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 585-586)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Spring 1989 Meeting - Agenda, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 587)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Fall 1988 Meeting - Agenda (Box 51, Folder 588)